A Guide to the Rockefeller Family and Associates (Room 5600), General Files, 1962-1996, Index Cards, RG 3-RG 44 FA1502
Rockefeller Archive Center
Rockefeller Family and Associates (Room 5600), General Files, 1962-1996, Index Cards, RG 3-RG 44
Rockefeller Archive Center
Rockefeller, David
Rockefeller, Laurance Spelman
Rockefeller, Nelson A. (Nelson Aldrich)
Rockefeller, John D., III (John Davison), 1906-1978
Mauze, Abby Rockefeller
FA1502
46.7 Cubic Feet 148 4x6 index card boxes, 107 microfilm reels
Arrangement
Cards are arranged alphabetically.
Scope and Contents
Index card files describing the contents of the Rockefeller Family & Associates General Files, 1962-1991 (Record Groups 3, 33, 37 and 39) as well as the David Rockefeller General Files, 1992-1996 and the Laurance S. Rockefeller General Files, 1992-1996.
Conditions Governing Access
Open for research.
Related Materials
FA094 Rockefeller Family and Associates (Room 5600), General Files, 1962-1976.
- Rockefeller Family and Associates (Room 5600), General Files 1962-1991 (Paper Cards), 1-RG 3-RG 39; 43.2 Cubic Feet 140 4x6 index card boxes.
  - A-Adj, 1962-1991 (Box 1)
  - Adm-Alexandre, 1962-1991 (Box 2)
  - Alexi-Am. Comer. Soc., 1962-1991 (Box 3)
  - American Canoe-Americana, 1962-1991 (Box 4)
  - Ames-Appalachin, 1962-1991 (Box 5)
  - Ara-Asia Society, 1962-1991 (Box 6)
  - Association-B, 1962-1991 (Box 7)
  - Ba-Baq, 1962-1991 (Box 8)
  - Bar-Bauc, 1962-1991 (Box 9)
  - Baur-Ben, 1962-1991 (Box 10)
  - Beng-Bethlehem, 1962-1991 (Box 11)
  - Bi-Blau, 1962-1991 (Box 12)
  - Ble-Blu, 1962-1991 (Box 13)
  - Bor-Bradley, 1962-1991 (Box 14)
  - Bram-Bro, 1962-1991 (Box 15)
  - Bron-Bryan, 1962-1991 (Box 16)
  - Bub-Burr, 1962-1991 (Box 17)
  - Bus-California, 1962-1991 (Box 18)
  - Call-Cara, 1962-1991 (Box 19)
  - Caribbean-Cast, 1962-1991 (Box 20)
  - Catholic-Chambers, 1962-1991 (Box 21)
  - Chambers-Children, 1962-1991 (Box 22)
  - Children-Citizens, 1962-1991 (Box 23)
  - Citizens H- Clint, 1962-1991 (Box 24)
  - Coa-Colorado, 1962-1991 (Box 25)
  - Columbia Univ.-Cong, 1962-1991 (Box 26)
  - Connecticut-Cove, 1962-1991 (Box 27)
  - Cornell Univ-Cran, 1962-1991 (Box 28)
  - Crawford-Curr, 1962-1991 (Box 29)
  - Cus-Daru, 1962-1991 (Box 30)
  - David-Declaration, 1962-1991 (Box 31)
  - Deer-Dennis, 1962-1991 (Box 32)
  - Dep-Dig, 1962-1991 (Box 33)
  - Dil-Dorado, 1962-1991 (Box 34)
  - Douglas-Dun, 1962-1991 (Box 35)
  - Dunn-Eco, 1962-1991 (Box 36)
  - Ede-Ellis, 1962-1991 (Box 37)
  - Elm-Esa, 1962-1991 (Box 38)
  - Esp-Family, 1962-1991 (Box 39)
  - Far-Ferr, 1962-1991 (Box 40)
  - Fi-Five, 1962-1991 (Box 41)
  - Flau-Fort, 1962-1991 (Box 42)
  - Foru-Freel, 1962-1991 (Box 43)
  - French-Fund, 1962-1991 (Box 44)
  - Funn-Garr, 1962-1991 (Box 45)
  - Gas-Gia, 1962-1991 (Box 46)
  - Gil-Gold, 1962-1991 (Box 47)
  - Goldman-Gra, 1962-1991 (Box 48)
  - Grah-Greenrock, 1962-1991 (Box 49)
  - Greenrock (cont.)-Gug, 1962-1991 (Box 50)
  - Bum-Halla, 1962-1991 (Box 51)
  - Ham-Harlem, 1962-1991 (Box 52)
  - HarrHass, 1962-1991 (Box 53)
  - Hau-Help, 1962-1991 (Box 54)
  - Hena-Hig, 1962-1991 (Box 55)
  - Hill-Hol, 1962-1991 (Box 56)
  - Holl-Hot, 1962-1991 (Box 57)
  - House-Hun, 1962-1991 (Box 58)
  - Hunter-India, 1962-1991 (Box 59)
  - Inf-Int'l.-D, 1962-1991 (Box 60)
  - Int'l House-Jab, 1962-1991 (Box 61)
  - JHPI-Jenkins, 1962-1991 (Box 62)
  - Jersey-Jones, 1962-1991 (Box 63)
  - Jones J-Kao, 1962-1991 (Box 64)
  - Kap-Kem, 1962-1991 (Box 65)
  - Kennedy-King J, 1962-1991 (Box 66)
  - Kings-Ko, 1962-1991 (Box 67)
  - Kol-Kul, 1962-1991 (Box 68)
  - Kuss-Lang, 1962-1991 (Box 69)
  - Lanh-Leb, 1962-1991 (Box 70)
  - Le C-Lev, 1962-1991 (Box 71)
  - Levitt-Lion, 1962-1991 (Box 72)
  - Lip-Loo, 1962-1991 (Box 73)
  - Los-Mab, 1962-1991 (Box 74)
  - Mac-Mal, 1962-1991 (Box 75)
  - Mall-Mark, 1962-1991 (Box 76)
  - Mars-Mato, 1962-1991 (Box 77)
  - Matt-McCo, 1962-1991 (Box 78)
  - McCr-McM, 1962-1991 (Box 79)
  - McN-Mer, 1962-1991 (Box 80)
  - Merr-Miller, 1962-1991 (Box 81)
  - Miller (cont.)- Mo, 1962-1991 (Box 82)
  - Moe-Mor, 1962-1991 (Box 83)
  - Morgan-Mount, 1962-1991 (Box 84)
  - Mountain-Museum, 1962-1991 (Box 85)
  - Museum of Primitive Art-NAACP, 1962-1991 (Box 86)
  - National C-Nationwide, 1962-1991 (Box 87)
  - Native-New Jersey, 1962-1991 (Box 88)
  - New York-NY State Abortion, 1962-1991 (Box 89)
  - NYU-No, 1962-1991 (Box 90)
  - Nolte-Nz, 1962-1991 (Box 91)
  - O-Old, 1962-1991 (Box 92)
  - Olsen-Org, 1962-1991 (Box 93)
  - Oss-P.I.P.C., 1962-1991 (Box 94)
  - Pan-Patti, 1962-1991 (Box 95)
  - Pauls-Peri, 1962-1991 (Box 96)
  - Perry- Philo, 1962-1991 (Box 97)
  - Pi - Polanco, 1962-1991 (Box 98)
  - Poland - Pr, 1962-1991 (Box 99)
  - Presbyterian - Prop, 1962-1991 (Box 100)
  - Pu - Ra, 1962-1991 (Box 101)
  - Raf - Recreation, 1962-1991 (Box 102)
  - Reed -Rey, 1962-1991 (Box 103)
  - Rey (cont.) - Riv, 1962-1991 (Box 104)
  - Riverside - Memberships, 1962-1991 (Box 105)
  - Property - Rodman, R, 1962-1991 (Box 106)
  - Rodman, R (cont.) - Ros, 1962-1991 (Box 107)
  - Ros (cont.)- Rudolph, 1962-1991 (Box 108)
  - Ruh - Saint or St., 1962-1991 (Box 109)
  - Saint I - San, 1962-1991 (Box 110)
  - Sand - Sc, 1962-1991 (Box 111)
  - Scha - Schu, 1962-1991 (Box 112)
  - Schwartz - Seg, 1962-1991 (Box 113)
  - Sem - She, 1962-1991 (Box 114)
  - Shelton - Sih, 1962-1991 (Box 115)
  - Sin - Sk, 1962-1991 (Box 116)
  - Sla - Smith, S., 1962-1991 (Box 117)
  - Smith - Sos, 1962-1991 (Box 118)
  - South - Spr, 1962-1991 (Box 119)
  - Sta - Stephens, 1962-1991 (Box 120)
  - Stern - Str, 1962-1991 (Box 121)
  - Stri - Swa, 1962-1991 (Box 122)
  - Swe - Tar, 1962-1991 (Box 123)
  - Tau - th, 1962-1991 (Box 124)
  - Thomas- To, 1962-1991 (Box 125)
  - Ton - Tro, 1962-1991 (Box 126)
  - Tu - Union, 1962-1991 (Box 127)
  - United - Nat'l Park Ser., 1962-1991 (Box 128)
  - University - Valentine, 1962-1991 (Box 129)
  - Van - Vern, 1962-1991 (Box 130)
  - Vi - W, 1962-1991 (Box 131)
  - Wa - War, 1962-1991 (Box 132)
  - Warner - Webe, 1962-1991 (Box 133)
  - Wei - Western, 1962-1991 (Box 134)
  - Wet - Wi, 1962-1991 (Box 135)
  - Wil - Wilson, 1962-1991 (Box 136)
  - Wim - Wood, 1962-1991 (Box 137)
  - Wood (cont.) - XYZ, 1962-1991 (Box 138)
  - Yale University - Youth, 1962-1991 (Box 139)
  - ZBVI - Zu, 1962-1991 (Box 140)
- Rockefeller Family and Associates (Room 5600), General Files 1962-1991 (Microfilm), 2-RG 3-RG 39; 1.07 Cubic Feet 107 16mm microfilm reels; 107 16mm microfilm reels.
  - A-Ad, 1962-1991 (Reel 1)
  - Ad-Al, 1962-1991 (Reel 2)
  - Al-Am, 1962-1991 (Reel 3)
  - Am-An, 1962-1991 (Reel 4)
  - An-As, 1962-1991 (Reel 5)
  - As-Ba, 1962-1991 (Reel 6)
  - Ba, 1962-1991 (Reel 7)
  - Ba-Be, 1962-1991 (Reel 8)
  - Be, 1962-1991 (Reel 9)
  - Be-Bl, 1962-1991 (Reel 10)
  - Bl-Bo, 1962-1991 (Reel 11)
  - Bo-Br, 1962-1991 (Reel 12)
  - Br, 1962-1991 (Reel 13)
  - Br-Bu, 1962-1991 (Reel 14)
  - Bu-Ca, 1962-1991 (Reel 15)
  - Ca, 1962-1991 (Reel 16)
  - Ca, 1962-1991 (Reel 17)
  - Ca-Ch, 1962-1991 (Reel 18)
  - Ch, 1962-1991 (Reel 19)
  - Ch-Cl, 1962-1991 (Reel 20)
  - Cl-Co, 1962-1991 (Reel 21)
  - Co, 1962-1991 (Reel 22)
  - Co, 1962-1991 (Reel 23)
  - Co-Cu, 1962-1991 (Reel 24)
  - Cu-Da, 1962-1991 (Reel 25)
  - Da-De, 1962-1991 (Reel 26)
  - De-Di, 1962-1991 (Reel 27)
  - Di-Do, 1962-1991 (Reel 28)
  - Do-Ea, 1962-1991 (Reel 29)
  - Ea-El, 1962-1991 (Reel 30)
  - El-Es, 1962-1991 (Reel 31)
  - Es-Fa, 1962-1991 (Reel 32)
  - Fe-Fi, 1962-1991 (Reel 33)
  - Fi-Fo, 1962-1991 (Reel 34)
  - Fo-Fr, 1962-1991 (Reel 35)
  - Fr-Ga, 1962-1991 (Reel 36)
  - Ga-Ge, 1962-1991 (Reel 37)
  - Ge-Go, 1962-1991 (Reel 38)
  - Go-Gr, 1962-1991 (Reel 39)
  - Gr, 1962-1991 (Reel 40)
  - Gr-Ha, 1962-1991 (Reel 41)
  - Ha, 1962-1991 (Reel 42)
  - Ha, 1962-1991 (Reel 43)
  - Ha-He, 1962-1991 (Reel 44)
  - He-Ho, 1962-1991 (Reel 45)
  - Ho, 1962-1991 (Reel 46)
  - Ho-Ii, 1962-1991 (Reel 47)
  - Ii - In, 1962-1991 (Reel 48)
  - In-Ja, 1962-1991 (Reel 49)
  - Ja-Jo, 1962-1991 (Reel 50)
  - Jo-Ka, 1962-1991 (Reel 51)
  - Ka-La, 1962-1991 (Reel 52)
  - La-Le, 1962-1991 (Reel 53)
  - Le-Li, 1962-1991 (Reel 54)
  - Li-Lo, 1962-1991 (Reel 55)
  - Lo-Mac, 1962-1991 (Reel 56)
  - Mac-Man, 1962-1991 (Reel 57)
  - Man-Mar, 1962-1991 (Reel 58)
  - Ma, 1962-1991 (Reel 59)
    Scope and Contents
    Reel is missing and unavailable for research.
  - Mc, 1962-1991 (Reel 60)
  - Mc-Me, 1962-1991 (Reel 61)
  - Me-Mi, 1962-1991 (Reel 62)
  - Mi-Mo, 1962-1991 (Reel 63)
  - Mo-Mu, 1962-1991 (Reel 64)
  - Mu-Na, 1962-1991 (Reel 65)
  - Na, 1962-1991 (Reel 66)
  - Na-Ne, 1962-1991 (Reel 67)
  - Ne-Ni, 1962-1991 (Reel 68)
  - Ni-Ny, 1962-1991 (Reel 69)
  - Ny-O'N, 1962-1991 (Reel 70)
  - O'N-Pa, 1962-1991 (Reel 71)
  - Pa, 1962-1991 (Reel 72)
  - Pa-Pe, 1962-1991 (Reel 73)
  - Pe-Pi, 1962-1991 (Reel 74)
  - Pi-Po, 1962-1991 (Reel 75)
  - Po-Pt, 1962-1991 (Reel 76)
  - Pu-Ra, 1962-1991 (Reel 77)
  - Ra-Re, 1962-1991 (Reel 78)
  - Re-Ri, 1962-1991 (Reel 79)
  - Ri-Ro, 1962-1991 (Reel 80)
  - Ro, 1962-1991 (Reel 81)
  - Ro-Ru, 1962-1991 (Reel 82)
  - Ru-Sa, 1962-1991 (Reel 83)
  - Sa, 1962-1991 (Reel 84)
  - Sa-Se, 1962-1991 (Reel 85)
  - Sc-Sh, 1962-1991 (Reel 86)
  - Sh-Si, 1962-1991 (Reel 87)
  - Si-Sl, 1962-1991 (Reel 88)
  - Sl-Sn, 1962-1991 (Reel 89)
  - So-Sp, 1962-1991 (Reel 90)
  - Sp-St, 1962-1991 (Reel 91)
  - St, 1962-1991 (Reel 92)
  - Su-Ta, 1962-1991 (Reel 93)
  - Ta-Th, 1962-1991 (Reel 94)
  - Th-To, 1962-1991 (Reel 95)
  - To-Tu, 1962-1991 (Reel 96)
  - Tu-United States Government, 1962-1991 (Reel 97)
  - United States Government-Va, 1962-1991 (Reel 98)
  - Va-Vi, 1962-1991 (Reel 99)
  - Vi-Wa, 1962-1991 (Reel 100)
  - Wa-We, 1962-1991 (Reel 101)
  - We-Wh, 1962-1991 (Reel 102)
  - Wh-Wi, 1962-1991 (Reel 103)
  - Wi-Wo, 1962-1991 (Reel 104)
  - Wo-Wy, 1962-1991 (Reel 105)
  - Wy-Za, 1962-1991 (Reel 106)
  - Za-Zy, 1962-1991 (Reel 107)
- David Rockefeller and Laurance S. Rockefeller (Room 5600) General Files 1992-1996, RG 43-RG 44; 2.4 Cubic Feet Eight 4x6 index card boxes.
  - A-B, 1992-1996 (Box 1)
  - C-D, 1992-1996 (Box 2)
  - E-H, 1992-1996 (Box 3)
  - H-L, 1992-1996 (Box 4)
  - M-O, 1992-1996 (Box 5)
  - P-S, 1992-1996 (Box 6)
  - S-V, 1992-1996 (Box 7)
  - W-Z, 1992-1996 (Box 8)